Heard of them
People from the Fu Group
Looks like they're not waiting for my text
You don't have to go
Why wouldn't I
They want to confirm
I want to know too
Then I'll go with you
Aren't you afraid I'll leave with the Fu Group
A little bit
Status can change
But our marriage certificate won't
Let's go, Mrs. Fu
You say that so naturally lately
It's legal
Mr. Fu
This is Elder Qin from the Fu Consortium
I've heard a lot about you, Mr. Fu
Elder Qin, the Gu Group provided some additional materials
But the payment uncertainty issue remains unresolved
What's your take, Mr. Fu
Mr. Lu
Now at every project meeting
we always have to ask Fu Chenzhou
Someone who can spot the problem
Is of course worth asking
The materials are more complete this time